http://www.hipaanswers.com/privacy-policy/

HIPAA Questions and Answers
Why is HIPAA important to patients?
What does PHI stand for?
Who Enforces HIPAA?
What Information is Protected by HIPAA?
What is the purpose of HIPAA?
What are the HIPAA Training Requirements?
HIPAA Law
When was HIPAA enacted?
About HIPAA Answers
Search for:
Home HIPAAnswers Privacy Policy
HIPAAnswers Privacy Policy
This privacy policy
discloses the privacy practices for HIPAAnswers.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website, including what personally identifiable information is collected from you through HIPAAnswers.com.
Data Collection, Use, and Sharing
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will only share your information with a third party outside of our organization if
clearly stated as a sponsor, but otherwise not store your data on our own servers or share it with any other sponsor. We will never contact you via email on the phone in the future.
Data Control
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. The newsletter is an automated system that allows you to unsubscribe at any time. There will not no other way that you will be contacted by HIPAAnswers.com.
Security
We take care to protect your information. When you submit personal information via the website, it is transmitted directly to a single sponsor and not stored on any internal database.
Video TrainingEngaging ContentPerfect RefresherFlexible/ConvenientSelf-paced Learning
Video Training – Engaging Content – Perfect RefresherFlexible/Convenient – Self-paced Learning
Free HIPAA Fundamentals Training
Full Course – Immediate Access
Privacy Policy
×
